#### Contact

shubhobera98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shubho09 (LinkedIn) shubhojeetbera.tech (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Adobe Premiere Pro Video Editing Web Development

## Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
Bengali (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

C++ Programming
IBM Blockchain Foundation
Developer V2

Responsive Web Design

**Blockchain Basics** 

JavaScript - Basics to Advanced

# Shubhojeet Bera

Web Developer | Video Editor | Blockchain Enthusiast. Durg

## Summary

Hey! I'm an Editor | Programmer | Blockchain enthusiast.

Worked as an editor with one of the top educators.

Have over 2.5+ years of experience in Content Creation, had over 60k+ Followers (Youtube + Instagram).

Rather than editing videos, I'm a productive programmer who just loves new technology. Very much interested in Blockchain, Crypto, Defi, DApps, DAOs, NFTs, and more.

For more: https://linktr.ee/shubho09

## Experience

#### YouTube

Video Editor @Ashish Futtan Vlogs January 2022 - April 2022 (4 months)

- Worked with a Youtube Vlogger, edited and managed his channel. Helped him to grow immensely.
- Till now edited over 50+ vlogs for their channel.

## Unacademy GATE & ESE

Video Editor @Engineering OGs January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

- Worked with one of the leading educators of this platform.
- Edited strategic content for aspirants of GATE/ESE (specifically).
- Edited over 40+ videos on their channel (includes Topper Interviews, Strategy to crack GATE/ESE & Podcasts).

## Education

Shri Shankaracharya Technical Campus

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2020 - 2024)

Khalsa Public Higher Secondary School Science · (2007 - 2020)